PayPro Global, Inc. Privacy policy

1\. PayPro Global Privacy Statement

Your privacy is important to us – we would like to ensure that you have a positivebuying experience in our store and hope to be able to welcome you back manytimes. We have created a set of privacy rules for us and our suppliers in order toguarantee you maximum privacy when shopping at PayPro Global Web site.

Please note that certain information is necessary to fulfil your order and

authorize your payment – however, we do not collect any data without yourconsent. This statement is based on the OECD guidelines for user privacy which

you will find below.

2\. About PayPro Global

Today’s information and communication technologies are a central part ofPayPro Global’s business activities. Our principal activity is DownloadableProduct Distribution Services for companies and buyers alike. Protecting yourprivacy and your personal data is an important aspect of the way we create,

organize and implement our activities on-line and off-line. Our privacy policy

covers PayPro Global, Inc. and all its subsidiaries.

Data Controller details:

PayPro Global Inc.Address: 225 The East Mall, Suite 1117, Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, Canada

Phone: +1-646-873-6857 Ext:704 Fax: +1-416-981-7818

URL: www.payproglobal.com

3\. Purpose Specification and Data Collection

You can access our Web site home page and browse our sites without disclosingpersonal data. We collect your personal data only with your knowledge or yourconsent. Aside from your automatically logged information, we do not collect anyother data about you. We collect the personal data that you volunteer onregistration, order, survey, competition, other forms or by email.

Overview of data processing provisions for customers of PayPro Global:

https://payproglobal.com/users-data-protection/

For any inquiries on the matter, you may contact us at:dataprotection@payproglobal.com

225 The East Mall, Suite 1117,Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, CanadaPhone (international): +1-647-977-7769Phone (USA/Canada toll free): +1-888-317-4868 www.payproglobal.com

225 The East Mall, Suite 1117,Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, CanadaPhone (international): +1-647-977-7769Phone (USA/Canada toll free): +1-888-317-4868 www.payproglobal.com

4\. Cookies

We use cookies only with your explicit consent in order to hold sessioninformation, improve security during a visitor’s session online or to improve theusability of our website during a visit. We do not associate the informationstored in a visitor’s cookie with any other personal data about that visitorwithout the user’s prior consent. Each of our employees having access to yourpersonal data and associated with the processing of that data is required to

respect the confidentiality of your personal data.

Privacy policies of the services involved are available under the following links:https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacyhttps://www.google.com/analytics/terms/

5\. Visitor Choice

You may choose to receive promotional or marketing information from ourwebsites if you choose to do so.

6\. Disclosure

We only disclose personal data about our website’s visitors to our associatedcompanies and their websites or – in case of electronic delivery – to thecompanies, from which you purchase products, for their information. They areallowed to use this information to provide you with technical support, informyou of product updates/upgrades or new releases. They are also required toallow you the ability to unsubscribe from the mailings. Your personal data willnot be disclosed to any other third party, especially not for the purpose ofmailings or any other marketing activity. We ensure that your personal data willnot be disclosed to state institutions and authorities except if required by law orother regulations.

7\. Privacy Policy

We have implemented technology and security policies, rules and measures toprotect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorizedaccess, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, accidentalloss.

225 The East Mall, Suite 1117,Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, CanadaPhone (international): +1-647-977-7769Phone (USA/Canada toll free): +1-888-317-4868 www.payproglobal.com

8\. Privacy Compliance Details

The Privacy Principles of the OECD Guidelines

- Collection Limitation Principle

There should be limits to the collection of personal data and any such datashould be obtained by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with theknowledge or consent of the user.

- Data Quality Principle

Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which they are to be used,to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete andkept up-to-date.

- Purpose Specification Principle

The purpose for which personal data is collected should be specified no laterthan at the time of collection and the subsequent use limited to the fulfillment of

those purposes or such others as are not incompatible with those purposes and

as are specified on each occasion of change of purpose.

- Use Limitation Principle

Personal data should not be disclosed, made available or otherwise used for

purposes other than those specified in accordance with Paragraph 9 (PurposeSpecification Principle) of the OECD Privacy Guidelines except:

a) with the consent of the data subject; orb) by the authority of law.

- Security Safeguards Principle

Personal data should be protected by reasonable security safeguards against

such risks as loss, unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or

disclosure of data.

- Openness Principle

There should be a general policy of openness about developments, practices andpolicies with respect to personal data. Means should be readily available byestablishing the existence and nature of personal data, and the main purposesof their use, as well as the identity and use of the Data Controller.

225 The East Mall, Suite 1117,Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, CanadaPhone (international): +1-647-977-7769Phone (USA/Canada toll free): +1-888-317-4868 www.payproglobal.com

- Individual Participation Principle

An individual should have the right:

a) to obtain from a data controller, or otherwise, confirmation of whether or notthe data controller has data relating to him;b) to have communicated to him data relating to him within a reasonable time:at a charge, if any, that is not excessive; in a reasonable manner; and in a formthat is readily intelligible to him; c) to be giver reasons if a request made undersubparagraphs (a) and (b) is denied, and to be able to challenge such denial; andd) to challenge data relating to him and, if the challenge is successful to have thedata erased, rectified, completed or amended.

- Accountability Principle

A Data Controller should be accountable for complying with measures which give

effect to the principles stated above.

9\. Privacy of Minors

Individuals under the age of eighteen (18) should not transfer any Personal

Information to us. We will neither purposely ask for their Personal Information,nor intentionally process it.

10\. Contact Us

To contact us in writing please address your inquiry to:

PayPro Global Inc.225 The East Mall, Suite 1117, Toronto, ON, M9B 0A9, Canada

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or other compliance-relatedmatters, please contact us at compliance@payproglobal.com.

Best PDF Encryption Reviews
